(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T14:15:05.659536",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
推しの曲 めっちゃいいね
"Your oshi's song is so good!"
みるハコチャーン！
"Miruhako Chaaan!"
みるハコなら
"With Miruhako,"
臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
"you can fully immerse yourself in your oshi's content!"
みるハコ最高！
"Miruhako is the best!"
推し活増やそう、みるハコ！
"Let's increase our oshi activities, Miruhako!"
第3弾
"Part 3"
「夜明けのうた」をよりお楽しみいただくために
To enjoy "Yoake no Uta" even more,
Blue Journey 今回の旅は、歌と朗読で紡いだ、ひとつの物語のようなライブです。
Blue Journey's journey this time is a story-like live woven with songs and reading.
短い旅ではございますが、心に残る体験をしていただきたいと考えています。
Though it is a short journey, we hope you will have a memorable experience.
旅に間に合うよう、時間に余裕を持ったご準備をお願いいたします。
Please make preparations in advance so you can make it in time.
推しの曲、めっちゃいいよね！
Your favorite's song is so good!
みるハコチャンス！
Miruhako Chance!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miruhako, you can enjoy your favorite's content with full immersion!
みるハコ最高！推し活を増やそう、みるハコ
Miruhako is the best! Let's boost our fan activities with Miruhako!
本日は「Blue Journey 1st Live 夜明けのうた」にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending today's "Blue Journey 1st Live: Song of Dawn."
開演に先立ちまして、お客さまにご注意並びにご案内申し上げます。
Before the show begins, we would like to make a few important announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and video recording equipment are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮下さいますようお願い申し上げます。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、体調に異変を感じる場合には、無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
If you feel unwell at any time, please notify a staff member immediately.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、カタグルマ、ステージ上に物を投げ込む、ステージ上に上がる、故意に通路をふさぐ、前に押し寄せる、周りのお客さまのご迷惑となるような
Mosh pits, crowdsurfing, carrying on shoulders, throwing objects onto the stage, blocking aisles, and pushing forward...
不自然なコール、規制、公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らすなどの行為、不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、腕を振り回す、上半身をそらすなどの過激な応援行為、
making disruptive noises, violently swinging arms at unnatural timings, and excessive cheering are strictly prohibited.
過度なジャンプ行為など、他のお客さまのご迷惑となる、または公演を妨げる禁止行為は一切禁止です。本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席のお客さまの様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Cameras for video streaming and photography may be present, and audience members may appear in footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了解ください。
Please be aware that these images and videos may be used for promotional purposes.
それでは、まもなく開演いたします。お席についてお待ちください。
The performance will begin shortly. Please take your seats and wait.
ブルージェニーの今回の旅は
Blue Journey's journey this time
歌と朗読で紡いだひとつの物語のようなライブです。
is a live performance woven together with songs and readings like a single story.
短い旅ではございますが、
It's a short journey, but
皆様の心に残る体験を皆さまと一緒に作っていきたいと考えています。
we hope to create an experience that stays in your hearts, together with all of you.
これに際して、会場の皆様にお願いがございます。
Regarding this, we have a request for everyone in the venue.
静かなパートなどで激しい声援を送るなど
Please refrain from cheering in ways that hinder the production,
演出の妨げとなるような応援はお控えください。
such as sending loud cheers during quiet parts.
ブルージェニーの今回の旅は、
Blue Journey's journey this time,
歌と朗読で紡いだひとつの物語のようなライブです。
is a live performance woven with songs and readings like a single story.
短い旅ではございますが、
It's a short journey, but
皆様の心に残る体験を皆様と一緒に作っていきたいと考えています。
we hope to create an experience that stays in your hearts, together with all of you.
これに際して、会場の皆様にお願いがございます。
Regarding this, we have a request for everyone in the venue.
静かなパートなどで激しい声援を送るなど
Please refrain from cheering in ways that hinder the production,
演出の妨げとなるような応援はお控えください。
such as sending loud cheers during quiet parts.
また、ペンライトは青や白など
Also, for penlights, please use
ブルージェニーを表す色を主にとって応援をお願いいたします。
mainly colors representing Blue Journey, like blue or white, to cheer.
もちろんこれは推しかりや曲の照明演出に
Of course, this does not uniformly prohibit
沿った応援を一律禁止するものではございません。
cheering in line with member colors or song lighting production.
なお、オープニングに際しては1曲目の歌が
Also, for the opening, until the first song starts,
始まるまでは是非ペンライトを消してお楽しみください。
please turn off your penlights and enjoy.
曲が始まりましたらペンライトをつけて、
Once the song begins, turn on your penlights,
そこからは主に青や白などブルージェニーの色を使い
and from there, mainly using colors like blue and white of Blue Journey,
全力で応援をしてください。
please cheer with all your might.
それではブルージェニーファーストライブ
Now, please enjoy the Blue Journey 1st Live
夜明けの歌をお楽しみください。
"Song of Dawn".
僕らはどうして生きているのだろう
Why are we living?
僕らはどうして笑っているのだろう
Why are we smiling?
僕らはどうして怒っているのだろう
Why are we getting angry?
僕らはどうして
Why do we—
ごまかしたり
cover it up...
まったり
Relaxing,
嘘をついたり
telling lies,
意地張ったり
being stubborn,
素直になれなかったり
not being able to be honest,
迷ったり
getting lost,
信じなかったり
not believing,
矛盾したり
contradicting,
言えなかったり
not being able to say it,
傷つけ合ったり
hurting each other,
なくしてしまったり
losing things,
気づかないふりをしたり
pretending not to notice—
どうしてそんなことするんだろう
why do we do such things?
ただ一緒にいたいだけなのに
When I just want to be together...
ただ好きでいたいだけなのに
when I just want to love you...
ただ楽しくいたいだけなのに
when I just want to be happy...
繰り返す日々に感情がすり潰されて 行ったり来たりする毎日に嫌気が差して
My emotions are ground down by repeating days, and I grow sick of the daily back-and-forth,
怒りをぶつける言い訳に いつも誰かを使ったりしてる
always using someone as an excuse to vent my anger.
そんな人間が嫌いだ
I hate people like that.
そんな世界が嫌いだ
I hate a world like that.
そんなあいつが大嫌いだ
I utterly hate people like that.
そんな僕も大嫌いだ 大嫌いだ
I hate myself like that so much. I hate myself.
大嫌いなはずなのに 壊してしまうのが怖かった
Even though I should have hated it, I was afraid of breaking it.
守りたかったはずなのに 傷つけることが怖かった
Even though I should have wanted to protect it, I was afraid of hurting it.
大好きだったはずなのに 離れ離れになってしまった
Even though I should have loved it so much, we ended up drifting apart.
あの時 声を上げていれば
If I had raised my voice back then—
あの時 話し合っていれば
if we had talked things out back then—
あの時 ちゃんと伝えていれば 何かが変わっただろうか
if I had properly communicated back then, would something have changed?
これは そんな僕の物語
This is the story of someone like me.
例えば君の顔に 昔よりシワが増えても
Even if your face has more wrinkles than before,
僕がギターを想うように 弾けなくなっても
or if I can't play the guitar like I used to,
心の歌は君で溢れているよ
my heart is overflowing with songs for you.
僕らは ひとりだ
We are all alone...
叱られるのを恐れて走って
Running for fear of being scolded,
またほら今日も同じ道通り過ぎていく
look, once again today we walk past the same path,
景色を見て 自分から目を逸らす
looking at the scenery and turning our eyes away.
そうじゃない こんなはずじゃなかったな
That's not it... it wasn't supposed to be like this.
そうだろ そうだろ
Am I right? Am I right?
生き聞かせてた 不安だって さぁ
I kept telling myself, even with all this anxiety, come on!
後悔の連続ばかりで 失ってばかりなんだ
Filled with endless regrets, I've done nothing but lose things.
失敗も後悔も全部やり直したいのに
Even though I want to redo all my failures and regrets,
失って初めて気づいた 与えられてばっかの僕だ
I only realized it after losing them—I'm someone who was always given everything.
ああだから 僕は一人だ
Ah, that's why I'm all alone.
あの日の後悔が今日もよぎる 今でもずっと繰り返し
The regrets of that day cross my mind again today, repeating endlessly even now.
まだ見ぬ景色に 想いを留めて 日常に目を逸らす
Keeping my thoughts on unseen scenery, I turn my eyes away from everyday life.
いつまで ずっとこのままなの
Until when will things stay like this forever?
どうして どうして 分かりあえずに いつまでも
Why, why can't we ever understand each other?
失敗の連続ばかりで 間違ってばかりなんだ
Filled with endless mistakes, I've done nothing but get things wrong.
人生も関係も全部やり直したいのに
Even though I want to redo my whole life and relationships,
間違って初めて気づいた 諦めてばっかの僕だ
I only realized it after getting it wrong—I'm someone who always gave up.
ああだから 今もこのまま
Ah, that's why I'm still just like this.
十字架も 心の祭壇に なる かすんでいく過去
Even crosses become altars in my heart as the past grows hazy—
傷口と幻影 痛みも忘れてしまうなら
if I'm going to forget the pain of wounds and illusions,
思い出すよ ここにあったと
I'll remember that it was right here.
だから僕は
That's why I...
チラ見せパートは間も無く終了です 続きは配信プラットフォーム「Z-aN」「SPWN」でご視聴ください
[Preview segment ending soon. Please watch the rest on streaming platforms Z-aN and SPWN.]
借りて失ってばかりだった
I just kept borrowing and losing things,
失敗も後悔も全部やり直したいんだ
wanting to redo all my failures and regrets.
今さら初めて気づいた いつだってバカは僕だ
I realized it for the first time—I've always been a fool.
ああ…
Ah...
だから 僕は一人だ
That's why I'm all alone.
無料部分は終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free portion has ended! Thank you for watching!